Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, 1918-2006
  - Subseries A: Contact Sheets with Shoot Numbers
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, Statler Hilton, Washington, D.C. Participants include Arnold Miller. Photos by Garry Tyler., May 26, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730120)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Supports United Farm Workers boycott of grapes and lettuce, A&P Supermarket, Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Donna Ristorucci., May 26, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730121)
    - Judy Edelman at Daily World. Photos by J. J. Johnson., May 30, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730122)
    - Demonstration for Day Care, Columbia University, New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson., May 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730124)
    - Demonstration Against Frank Hogan (District Attorney) and in Support of Carlos Feliciano., Jun 2, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730125)
    - Puerto Rican Day Parade, Young Workers Liberation League and Communist Party of the United States of America contingent, New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Jun 3, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730126)
    - Demonstration for Day Care, First National City Bank, New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson, Jun 4, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730127)
    - Joe Alexander, Bobby Gleason's Gym, Bronx, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730128)
    - Rally and March in Defense of Carlos Feliciano, 100 Centre Street, New York, New York. Photos by Miriam Gomez., Jun 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730129)
    - Track Meet between Soviet Union and United States Teams, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York. Photos by Ron Tyson., Jun 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730130)
    - Felix Ojeda Birthday Party. Participants include Gus Hall, David Perez, Jose Ristorucci and Charlene Mitchell., Jun 9, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730131)
    - MS Mikhail Lermontov (Soviet Union ocean liner) in New York Harbor. Don McMillan and Dmitri Shostakovich pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 11, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730132)
    - Thami Mhlambiso (African National Congress). Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 13, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730133)
    - Demonstration for Day Care, New York Times building, 43rd Street between 7th and 8th Avenues, New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jun 14, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730134)
    - Picketing Two Guys Department Store, North Bergen, New Jersey. Photos by Pat Barile., Jun 14, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730135)
    - Memorial Services for Arna Bontemps (writer), Riverside Church, New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jun 20, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730136)
    - Memorial Meeting for Julius and Ethel Rosenburg, Service Employees International Union (43rd Street and 8th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Charlene Mitchell, George Merritt, Rose Sobell, Pete Seeger and Morton Sobell. Photos by Ron Tyson., Jun 24, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730137)
    - Exhibit of Puerto Rican Art. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 25, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730138)
    - Jeanette Gomez (Communist Party of the United States of America candidate for New York City Council). Photos by Miriam Gomez., Jun 26, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730139)
    - Demonstration for ONEITA Workers, J. C. Penney department store (6th Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 28, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730143)
    - United Auto Workers Rank and File membership Meeting, Mahwah, New Jersey. Photos by Pat Barile., Jun 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730145)
    - Preservation Hall Jazz Band and Drootin Brothers Jazz Quartet, Staten Island Ferry. Drootin Brothers: Al Drootin (clarinet, soprano saxophone, tenor saxophone), Buzzy Drootin (drums), Sonny Drootin (piano), Tom Jordan (bass, banjo). Preservation Hall Jazz Band: Percy Humphrey (trumpet), Albert Burbank (clarinet), Frank Desmond (trombone), Narvin Kimball (banjo), Sing Miller (piano), Chester Zardis (bass), Dave Oxley (drums). Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 1, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730146)
    - Demonstration by Metropolitan Council On Housing for End to Maximum Base Rent Law, Office of Housing Commissioner Lee Goodwin (32nd Street and 7th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Rasheed Storey and David Perez., Jul 2, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730147)
    - Artwork by Palmer Hayden., Jul 3, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730148)
    - Newport Jazz Festival, Philharmonic Hall (66th Street and Broadway), New York, New York. Participants include, Joe Turner, Turk Murphy Band (Turk Murphy, Leon Oakley, Bob Helm, Pete Clute, Bill Caroll, Carl Lunceford and Jimmy Stanislaus), Wally Rose, Bob Greene Band (Ernie Carson, Herb Hall, Essie Resnick, Bob Greene, Danny Barker, Tommy Benford and Milt Hinton) and Preservation Hall Jazz Band (Percy Humphrey, Albert Burbank, Frank Desmond, Narvin Kimball, Sing Miller, Chester Jardis, Dave Oxley). Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 4, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730149)
    - Demonstration Against Poster Exhibit, Cultural Center (59th Street at Columbus Circle), Jul 5, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730150)
    - Judy Edelman. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730151)
    - Postal Workers Picket, 32nd Street and 8th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730152)
    - Art Hodes, Carnegie Hall (7th Avenue and 56th Street), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 7, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730153)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America candidates rally, Hotel McAlpin (34th Street and 6th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants includt The Mass Approach Singers, Rick Nagin, Amadeo Richardson, Frances Bordofsky, Rasheed Storey, Benny Giboyeaux, George Henning, Roque Ristorucci, Judy Edelman, Jose Stevens, Jeanette Gomez, John Gallo and Sam Perez. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 8, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730154)
    - Demonstration Against Hernandez Colon's (Puerto Rican governor) Cooperation with United States Imperialism. Participants include Sam Perez, John Gallo and Benny Giboyeaux., Jul 9, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730155)
    - Demonstration to Keep Community School Board Site, Lower East Side neighborhood, New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Jul 11, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730156)
    - Demonstration for Abolition of Maximum Base Rent Law, Nelson Rockefeller's Office (55th Street), New York, New York. Participants include Georgia Henning and Roque Ristorucci., Jul 12, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730157)
    - MS Mikhail Lermontov (Soviet Union ocean liner) at World Trade Center, New York, New York. Joseph North, Art Shields and Don McMillan pictured. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 12, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730158)
    - Demonstration for Right to Paint a Mural. Lucy Mahler pictured. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 16, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730160)
    - Bolshoi Ballet Rehearsal. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 18, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730161)
    - Demonstration for Carabanchel Ten, 46th Street and 5th Avenue, New York, New York. Participants include Moe Foner (frame 17), Leon Davis (fram 19) and Moe Fishman (frame 32). Photos by Pat Barile., Jul 18, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730162)
    - Rasheed Storey, Albany, New York. Photos by Amadeo Richardson., Jul 24, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730164)
    - World Youth Festival delegation leaves New York for Berlin., Jul 26, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730165)
    - Tenth World Youth Festival, Berlin, German Democratic Republic. Opening Ceremony at Stadium of Youth. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 28, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730166)
    - Tenth World Youth Festival, Berlin, German Democratic Republic. Meeting Between United States and Vietnamese Delegations. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 29, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730167)
    - Tenth World Youth Festival, Berlin, German Democratic Republic. Solidarity meeting between national liberation movements in Angola, Mozambique and Guinea-Bissau, Solidarity meeting between United States and Soviet Union. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 28, 1973 - Aug 5, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730168)
    - Tenth World Youth Festival, Berlin, German Democratic Republic. Angela Davis speaking. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 28, 1973 - Aug 5, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730169)
    - Tenth World Youth Festival, Berlin, German Democratic Republic. United States National Cultural Show. Participants include Joe Bataan, Line Weber, Carl Skameg, Mass Approach Singers. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 28, 1973 - Aug 5, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730170)
    - Tenth World Youth Festival, Berlin, German Democratic Republic. Scenes of Berlin and aerial pictures. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Jul 28, 1973 - Aug 5, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730171)
    - Demonstration Against Vietnam Veterans Losing Grants to Study at Art Students League, Nelson Rockefeller's office (55th Street), New York, New York., Jul 31, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730172)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Candidates at Street Fair, 15th Street, New York, New York. Georgia Henning, Roque Ristorucci and Rick Nagin Pictures. Photos by Pedro Perez., Jul 31, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730173)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Candidates, New York, New York. Roque Ristorucci, Georgia Henning, John Gallo, Benigno Giboyeaux, Judy Edelman, Samuel Perez, Rasheed Storey pictured. Photos by Ted Reich., Jul 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730174)
    - Georgia Henning Participates in Housing Action, New York, New York., Aug 4, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730177)
    - Picket and Sit-In at Gulf and Western Against Badge 373(movie), Columbus Circle, New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Aug 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730178)
    - Henry Winston and Gus Hall Look Over Winston's New Book "Strategy for a Black Agenda," 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York., Aug 6, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730179)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Certification Meeting About Columbia Presbyterian Hospital, Audubon Ballroom (Broadway and 165th Street), New York, New York. Doris Turner (frames 30-32) pictured. Photos by Pat Barile., Aug 7, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730180)
    - Demonstration Against United States Imperialism in Puerto Rico, United Nations (44th Street and 1st Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Aug 13, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730182)
    - Crew members of MS Mikhail Lermontov (Soviet Union ocean liner) Perform at United Nations, New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Aug 14, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730183)
    - Puerto Ricans at Plaza Borinquen, Bronx, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Aug 15, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730184)
    - Inquiring Photographer, 8th Avenue and 39th Street, New York, New York., Aug 16, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730185)
    - Demonstration Against Israeli Aggression by Students, Israeli Mission to the United Nations, 2nd Avenue and 42nd Street, New York, New Yrok. Photos by Pedro Perez., Aug 21, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730186)
    - Soviet Youth Delegation Visits United States. Photos by Sumner Jones., Aug 28, 1973 - Aug 29, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730187)
    - Demonstration Against Rockefeller Drug Laws. Participants include Charles Kenyatta (frame 17-21). Photos by Joe Popper., Aug 29, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730188)
    - Vietnam Veterans Protest Over Lack of Jobs, Veterans Administration, 252 7th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Jose Perez., Aug 29, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730190)
    - Attempted Arson at Communist Party of the United States of America Offices, 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Aug 29, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730191)
    - Demonstration in support of Carlos Feliciano, Nelson Rockefeller's Office (55th Street), New York, New York. Participants include Mike Myerson, Roque Ristorucci and Charlene Mitchell. Photos by Joe Popper., Aug 30, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730192)
    - Demonstration Against High Food Prices, Columbia University, New York, New York. Photos by Ron Tyson, Aug 31, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730193)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America and Young Workers Liberation League protest Gulf Oil holdings in Portugal's African colonies. Harlem, New York, New York. Participants include Jose Stevens and Dave Bailey. Photos by Ron Tyson., Sep 1, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730194)
    - Eastern New York Correctional Facility, Napanoch, New York. Photos by Joe Popper., Sep 4, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730195)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 demonstration in Support of United Farm Workers, A&P headquarters, Lexington Avenue and 45th Street, New York, New York. Participants include Moe Foner and Ed Koch., Sep 4, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730196)
    - Demonstration Against Racist Board Members at District One, Lower East Side neighborhood, New York, New York. Photos by Ron Tyson and Pedro Perez., Sep 7, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730198)
    - Artwork from El Museo del Barrio. Photos by Sumner Jones., Sep 7, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730199)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1518 members On Strike, Selgina Electric Company., Sep 7, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730200)
    - Daily World Picnic, Arrow Park, Monroe, New York. Participants include Pete Seeger, Henry Winston, Roque Ristorucci, Judy Edelman and Matty Berkleheimer. Photos by J. J. Johnson and Sumner Jones., Sep 9, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730201)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Demonstration in Support of Employees on Strike, Columbia University, New York, New York. Photos by Joe Popper., Sep 10, 1973 (Box 37, Shoot 730203)
    - Demonstration Against Coup in Chile, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania., Sep 11, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730205)
    - Memorial Rally and March for George Wiley, Welfare Center, 250 Church Street, New York, New York. Participants include Ralph Abernathy, Beulah Sanders, Frederick Douglass Kirkpatrick, Ossie Davis and Victor Gotbaum., Sep 12, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730206)
    - Women United for Action Demonstration Against High Food Prices, Federal Plaza (Foley Square), New York, New York. Participants include Ralph Abernathy, Frederick Douglass Kirkpatrick and Beulah Sanders. Photos by Ron Tyson., Sep 12, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730207)
    - Georgia Henning with Painting by Jack Bilander. Photos by Amadeo Richardson., Sep 13, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730209)
    - Rally on 2nd Anniversary of Attica Prison Massacre, Church of the Master, 122nd Street and Morningside Avenue, New York, New York. Participants include David Garcia (frames 19-21), Beulah Sanders (frame 22), Dolores Costello (frame 23), Roger Champen (frame 14), Mike Glick (frame 18), Sumner Jones (frame 11) and George Merritt (frame 30). Photos by Joe Popper., Sep 13, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730210)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Meeting. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Sep 13, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730211)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Strike and Student Sit-in, Columbia University, New York, New York., Sep 14, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730212)
    - Demonstration Against United States Involvement in Coup in Chile, from 47th Street and 1st Avenue to 42nd Street and 1st Avenue, then 50th Street and Park Avenue (International Telephone and Telegraph Company), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Sep 18, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730213)
    - Demonstration to Demand Unified Policy Towards Korea, United Nations, 47th Street and 1st Avenue, New York, New York., Sep 18, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730214)
    - Demonstration Against Newark Housing Authority Plan to Take Rent Directly from Welfare Department, Stella Wright Public Housing Project, Newark, New Jersey. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Sep 19, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730215)
    - Opening Party for Communist Party of the United States of America Election Campaign Headquarters, 23rd Street and 8th Avenue. Georgia Henning and Roque Ristorucci pictured. Photos by Amadeo Richardson., Sep 22, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730216)
    - Puerto Rico. Photos by Jose Ristorucci., Sep 22, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730217)
    - Mural, Wright Brothers School. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Sep 23, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730219)
    - Artwork by African American Artists. Photos by Sumner Jones., Sep 23, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730220)
    - Patricia Bell Blawis after Escape from Chilean Junta, Daily World office, 205 West 19th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Sep 24, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730221)
    - Demonstration and Rally for Puerto Rican Independence and Against Fascist Chilean Junta, United Nations (42nd Street and 1st Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Sep 24, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730222)
    - Richard Morford at Council for American Soviet Friendship, 150 5th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Sumner Jones., Sep 25, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730223)
    - Mike Clausell Interviewed by Joe Popper at Daily World., Sep 27, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730224)
    - Ken Newcomb, Communist Party of the United States of America Candidate for Governor of New York at Daily Worker, Sep 28, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730225)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Headquarters Firebombed, 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Oct 1, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730227)
    - Demonstration by Communist Party of United States of America in Support of Luis Corvalan, Chilean Embassy to the United Nations, 809 United Nations Plaza, New York, New York. Participants include William L. Patterson, Jarvis Tyner, Jose Ristorucci, Arnold Johnson, Helen Winter, Sondra Patrinos and Ken Newcomb.Photos by J. J. Johnson., Oct 3, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730228)
    - Tony Monteiro Speaking, Harlem Marxist Center (148th Street), New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Oct 6, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730229)
    - Demonstration Against Budget Cuts to New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, Nelson Rockefeller's Office (55th Street), New York, New York. Photos by Pedro Perez., Oct 9, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730230)
    - Rally to Protest Frame-up of Carlos Feliciano, 120 Centre Street, New York, New York. Participants include Angela Davis (frames 12-15). Photos by Pedro Perez., Oct 12, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730233)
    - Celebrating Completion of Mural, Wright Brothers School. Participants include Vicki Morris (frames 11-12) and Lucy Mahler (frame 2). Photos by Miriam Gomez., Oct 13, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730234)
    - Communist Party of the United States Candidates Discuss Issues, 268 West 23rd Street, New York, New York. Participants include Rasheed Storey, Judy Edelman, Georgia Henning and Dave Bailey. Photos by Amadeo Richardson., Oct 13, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730235)
    - Jeanette Gomez Campaigning, Bronx, New York. Eliseo Arroyo (frame 8), Miriam Gomez (frame 12) and Mike Scarpelli (frames 2-3) also pictured. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Oct 13, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730236)
    - Connecticut Coalition Against Racist and Political Repression. Photos by Joe Taylor., Oct 13, 1973 - Oct 14, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730237)
    - Memorial Tribute to Salvador Allende and Pablo Neruda, Town Hall, New York, New York. Participants include David Garcia, Gus Hall, Angela Davis, Al Evanoff, Sarah Cunningham, John Randolph, Beatrice Rippey, Caroll Hollister, Fernando Navarro and Carlos Russell. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 13, 1973 - Oct 14, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730238)
    - Daily World Staff Fernanda Navarro, Sumner Jones and Mike Giocondo., Oct 16, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730239)
    - Demonstration Against Cutting Welfare Services, Melrose Welfare Center (847 Morris Avenue), Bronx, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Oct 17, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730239)
    - Rally to Impeach Richard Nixon, 200 East 6th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Oct 20, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730240)
    - National Conference for Anti-Imperialist Solidarity with African Liberation, Chicago, Illinois. Participants include Charlotte Black, Claude Lightfoot, Caroline Black, Franklin Black, Angela Davis, Henry Winston and Charlene Mitchell. Photos by Sumner Jones., Oct 20, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730241)
    - United States Delegation to World Peace Congress in Moscow. John F. Kennedy Airport, New York, New York., Oct 23, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730242)
    - Demonstration Against Nelson Rockefeller's Transit Bond Steal Campaign., Oct 24, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730243)
    - Fernanda Navarro (Secretary to Allende Popular Unity government in Chile) Speaks at Daily World., Oct 25, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730244)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Candidates Campaign. Georgia Henning and John Gallo pictured. Photos by Amadeo Richardson., Oct 27, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730245)
    - Pat Bonner-Lyons Campaign, Boston, Massachusetts. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Oct 27, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730246)
    - Demonstration for Funding Coney Island Hospital, City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Oct 29, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730247)
    - Demonstration for Release of Puerto Rican Political Prisoners in United States, White House, Washington, D.C. Photos by Pedro Perez., Oct 30, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730249)
    - Views of New York City from Riverside Church, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Oct 31, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730250)
    - Demonstration Against Professors on War Contracts, Columbia University, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Oct 31, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730251)
    - Demonstration by Women Strike for Peace for Impeachment of Richard Nixon. Photos by Ron Tyson., Oct 31, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730252)
    - Demonstration for Coney Island Hospital, Brooklyn County Court and City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Nov 1, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730253)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Candidates Campaign, Garment Center, New York, New York. Roque Ristorucci, John Gallo, Rasheed Storey and Judy Edelman Pictured. Photos by Amadeo Richardson., Nov 1, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730254)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Hospital Workers on Strike. Photos by Joe Popper., Nov 5, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730255)
    - Demonstration Against Poverty in Coney Island, Mayor-Elect Abraham Beame's Office, New York, New York. Photos by J. J. Johnson., Nov 6, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730256)
    - New York City Uniformed Firefighters on Strike, 19th Street and 7th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Pat Barile., Nov 6, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730257)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union Retirees Demonstrate for Higher Pension, ILGWU Headquarters (55th Street and Broadway), New York, New York., Nov 8, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730258)
    - Rally to Impeach Richard Nixon. Participants include Sidney von Luther (frame 18)., Nov 10, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730259)
    - Committee Against Racism. Photos by Sumner Jones., Nov 17, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730260)
    - Jazz Concert in Memory of Eddie Condon, Hunter College, New York, New York. Participants include Dick Wellstood, Maxine Sullivan, Max Kaminsky and Milt Hinto. Photos by Bill Andrews., Nov 19, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730261)
    - Harry Epstein with Ellen Perlo and Sumner Jones at Daily World., Nov 20, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730262)
    - William Shockley (fascist ideologue) Speaks at Staten Island Community College. Photos by Sumner Jones., Nov 20, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730263)
    - Bill Andrews., Nov 24, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730264)
    - Harry Eisman with Simon Gerson and Art Shields at Daily World., Nov 30, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730265)
    - Street Theater Group Supports Farah Pants Strike, Macy's Department Store, 34th Street and 6th Avenue, New York, New York., Dec 1, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730267)
    - Demonstration Against United States Aid to Lon Nol Regime in Cambodia, United Nations, 42nd Street and 1st Avenue, New York, New York., Dec 1, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730268)
    - National Action Congress on Latin America Offices Bombed, 150 5th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Dec 3, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730270)
    - Demonstration by Puerto Rican Socialist Party over Lack of Coverage of Puerto Rican Independence Struggle, New York Times, New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Dec 4, 1973 (Box 38, Shoot 730271)